<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thought Voyager</title>
    <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thought Voyager</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thoughtvoyager.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Manifesto For The Future</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/a-manifesto-for-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/a-manifesto-for-the-future/</guid>
      <description>All good and well do you maybe think at this point after reading some of my ideas, but what is the way forward then? In this post I want to give a short manifesto for how I imagine the future to be.&#xA;Explanation in short Link to heading The future will be decentralized and sustainable where voluntary cooperation, market innovation and strong property rights foster community resilience without the need for (a) centralized authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Handbook For Revolutions</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/a-handbook-for-revolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/a-handbook-for-revolutions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This site uses what is called public learning. Feel free to look around!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case For Anarchy</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/the-case-for-anarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/the-case-for-anarchy/</guid>
      <description>In this post I want to defend the position for an anarchy based society. In my opinion is the concept of the state an relic from the past and do we need to go to another form of living. In my post [[The Failure Of Modern Day Democracy]] I already have argued I don´t believe in (modern day) democracy anymore. In this post I will lay out why no goverment/rule (anarchy) is the better option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Failure Of Modern Day Democracy</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/the-failure-of-modern-day-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/the-failure-of-modern-day-democracy/</guid>
      <description>In this post I want to explore the thought that modern day democracy has failed. I think modern day democracy doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a future. I will explain why and propose a new form of government that i think is the better option.&#xA;Why democracy doesn&amp;rsquo;t work in its current form Link to heading Most western countries have a democracy as government. The people choose who they want to represent them. This sounds good in practice, because if a lot of people vote who they want, the government will do anything that&amp;rsquo;s in the best interest of the people right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome-Welkom</title>
      <link>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/welcome-welkom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thoughtvoyager.com/posts/welcome-welkom/</guid>
      <description>This is my digital garden where you can explore my thoughts, as they grow to form fully fledged ideas. This site uses the concept of public learning. Go and explore the path you want!&#xA;Dit is mijn digitale tuin waar je mijn gedachten kunt verkennen, terwijl ze tot volledig vormgegeven gedachten vormen. Deze site maakt gebruik van het concept van publiek leren. Ga en verken het pad dat jij wil!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
