<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Input/Videos on Thought Voyager</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/input/videos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Input/Videos on Thought Voyager</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/input/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hidden/my-templates/inputs/video-notes-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hidden/my-templates/inputs/video-notes-template/</guid>
      <description> Notes Link to heading Highlights Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/-how-i-actually-use-my-commonplace-books-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/-how-i-actually-use-my-commonplace-books-/</guid>
      <description> Notes Link to heading Highlights Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/how-to-turn-your-notes-into-published-articles-and-books-using-the-obsidian-app-with-eleanor-konik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/how-to-turn-your-notes-into-published-articles-and-books-using-the-obsidian-app-with-eleanor-konik/</guid>
      <description> Notes Link to heading [[Turning notes into content]]&#xA;Highlights Link to heading 20:43 - Brainstorming Link to heading Initially have a main question that you try to find answers for in your vault Searches words related to topic in search Drags the list item into the file Instead of linking whole file, only links certain excerpt Uses specified links (headers, quotes) Crazy how passionate and expansive she is on the different topics she pulls Obsidian runs not on economy, but on knowledge economy Fiction can be used to extract fundamental ideas of human nature 34:16 - Ideas Link to heading Keep track of blog ideas Stages of content &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;seed&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;progress&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;published&amp;rdquo; last-updated Type: article, blog, etc 30:23 - MOC structure Link to heading Literature notes Books Pending articles Newsletters Unfinished literature Daily notes connections Atomic notes Can turn MOCS into articles 49:17 - CH#P# for keeping track on where she got quotes Link to heading 56:16 - Atomic notes Link to heading Has a block quote HTML tag, for quotes or for paraphrasing Uses it to have a highlight tag showcasing that it is paraphrased keeps atomic notes in their relative literature notes, just descriptive headings 59:50 - Reading logs and reflecting Link to heading Keeps it in daily note, links to the articles they consumed (whether external or something) Include a big takeaway from what you read, make a note and idea on it Daily notes includes headings to organize the day&amp;rsquo;s progress for easy review during the end of the week Minor tasks, reading log, accomplishments, gratitude 01:07:51 - Dataview in MOCS Link to heading Use it for unpolished MOC connections To be processed from &amp;quot;&amp;quot; 01:13:01 - Synthesizing Notes Link to heading Create an atomic idea and embed relevant snippets of other notes 01:18:15 - Musings to showcase curiosity, then turn into output Link to heading Thoughts/Questions Link to heading Bruh how did I not know this prior, I mean I guess my use case was mostly knowledge hoarding so this shit is life changing </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/obsidian-bookmarks---save-your-place-save-your-headspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/obsidian-bookmarks---save-your-place-save-your-headspace/</guid>
      <description> Summary Link to heading Notes Link to heading [[Obsidian Bookmarks]]&#xA;Highlights Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/stop-procrastinating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/stop-procrastinating/</guid>
      <description>Summary Link to heading Keep a workprogress log, feed the machine, make an event of your worst tasks, build a routine&#xA;Notes Link to heading Tip #1&#xA;Keep a workprogress log. Write down tasks and workblocks. Write down blocks and add a objective to it, when done mak it off.&#xA;Tip #2&#xA;Feed the machine: drink water continually. Monitor cafeïne intake. Check what you eat: glucose spike (!), skip breakfast: intermitting fasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/the-absolute-best-way-to-use-a-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-inputs/my-videos/the-absolute-best-way-to-use-a-notebook/</guid>
      <description>Summary Link to heading There are three types of notebooks: thoughts, experience, self-mastery. These categories have subtypes&#xA;Notes Link to heading What type of notebook: what is missing in your life?&#xA;Intellectual stimulation Space and time to think deeply Wisdom Inspiration Time management Life management Organizing your thoughts Recording and processing your experiences Three categories:&#xA;Thoughts Self-generated thoughts Figure out what you believe Think deeply Know thyself Type of notebooks: Journals Dianoia: just write something to think about and think about it Good-idea journal Book reviews Handbook: how to behave?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
